Guide to the David Skorton papers, 2006-2015.
Skorton, David papers
- Weill Institute Symposium, 2009-10-13 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Alice Fulton Literary Lunch, 2009-10-14 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Frank H. T. Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Award, 2009-10-16 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Lynch/Weiss Visit, 2009-10-17 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- CACO/CAA Board Meeting, 2009-10-17 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Hatfield Lecture, 2009-10-22 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Carnauba Memoir, 2009-10-22 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Friday Bailey Script, 2009-10-23 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Annual Fund Kick-Off, 2009-10-24 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- TCAM State of the University, 2009-10 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Miscellaneous Projects (June-October), 2009-10 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Global HR Forum, 2009-11-03-2011-11-04 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Global HR Forum - Liberal Education, 2009-11-05 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- Beijing All-Alumni, 2009-11-07 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- Beijing Forum, 2009-11-09 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Net Impact Conference, 2009-11-13 (Box 12, Folder 50)
- Lab of Ornithology Administrative Board, 2009-11-13 (Box 12, Folder 51)
- Paul Foremost Benefactor, 2009-11-13 (Box 12, Folder 52)
- D Rogers Health Policy Colloquium, 2009-11-18 (Box 12, Folder 53)
- Joseph Scheurer Scholarship, 2009-11-19 (Box 12, Folder 54)
- Teagle Foundation, 2009-11-20 (Box 12, Folder 55)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2009-11-20 (Box 12, Folder 56)
- Hockey Tailgate, 2009-11-28 (Box 12, Folder 57)
- Cornell Center for Sustainable Futures Statement, 2009-12-01 (Box 12, Folder 58)
- J. McConkey Literary Lunch, 2009-12-02 (Box 12, Folder 59)
- BME 4110 Lecture, 2009-12-03 (Box 12, Folder 60)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine, 2009-12-01 (Box 12, Folder 61)
- Academic Industry Collaboration, 2009-12-08 (Box 12, Folder 62)
- Governor's Task Force Press Conference, 2009-12-14 (Box 12, Folder 63)
- Climate Action Plan, 2009-12-16 (Box 12, Folder 64)
- January Graduates Reception, 2009-12-19 (Box 12, Folder 65)
- Miscellaneous Projects (October-December), 2009-12-01 (Box 12, Folder 66)
- Appel Celebration, 2010-01-13 (Box 12, Folder 67)
- Global Health Grand Rounds, 2010-01-13 (Box 12, Folder 68)
- Climate Action Meeting, 2010-01-15 (Box 12, Folder 69)
- Major Gifts Committee, 2010-01-20 (Box 12, Folder 70)
- President's Circle Dinner, 2010-01-20 (Box 12, Folder 71)
- IOM Nomination, 2010-01-20 (Box 12, Folder 72)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine, 2010-01-26 (Box 12, Folder 73)
- Haitian Student Association, 2010-01-28 (Box 12, Folder 74)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2010-01-29 (Box 12, Folder 75)
- NAICU Annual Meeting, 2010-02-01 (Box 12, Folder 76)
- BHEF Meeting, 2010-02-04-2010-02-05 (Box 12, Folder 77)
- Senior Class Campaign, 2010-02-08 (Box 12, Folder 78)
- Harris Dinner, 2010-02-11 (Box 12, Folder 79)
- Meinig Reception/Investment Committee, 2010-02-13 (Box 12, Folder 80)
- Better Housing Tompkins, 2010-02-16 (Box 12, Folder 81)
- G. Gellert Dedication, 2010-02-18 (Box 12, Folder 82)
- Cornell-Microsoft Videoconference, 2010-02-24 (Box 12, Folder 83)
- Africa-US Higher Education Summit, 2010-02-25-2010-02-26 (Box 12, Folder 84)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2010-02-26 (Box 12, Folder 85)
- 400 Club, 2010-03-01 (Box 12, Folder 86)
- Weill Reception for VetMed, 2010-03-02 (Box 12, Folder 87)
- Cardiology Interest Group, 2010-03-08 (Box 12, Folder 88)
- Asia Leadership Conference, 2010-03-09 (Box 12, Folder 89)
- Distinguished Chair Holders, 2010-03-12 (Box 12, Folder 90)
- Arts Quad Gathering, 2010-03-17 (Box 12, Folder 91)
- San Francisco Campaign Kick-Off, 2010-03-18 (Box 12, Folder 92)
- Cornell Silicon Valley Advisory Board, 2010-03-18 (Box 12, Folder 93)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine, 2010-03-30 (Box 12, Folder 94)
- Society for the Humanities, 2010-03-31 (Box 12, Folder 95)
- Sigma Pi Welcome, 2010-04-01 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2010-04-05 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Winter Sports Celebration, 2010-04-16 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Macaulay Event, 2010-04-08 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Council on Foreign Affairs India Panel, 2010-04-09 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Service Awards, 2010-04-12 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Cornell Days, 2010-04-12 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Spring Recognition Dinner, 2010-04-14 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- CEO Lunch, 2010-04-14 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- EYP - L. Olayan, 2010-04-15 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Clinton Global Initiative, 2010-04-16-2010-04-18 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Office Professionals Symposium, 2010-04-21 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Parents Campus Visit, 2010-04-23 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Ross Brann Celebration, 2010-04-25 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- International Students Reception, 2010-04-26 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Cook Awards Luncheon, 2010-04-27 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Senior Reception, 2010-04-27 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- CURB, 2010-04-28 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Perkins Prize, 2010-04-28 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Joint Service Clubs, 2010-04-28 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- PCCW Founders Dinner, 2010-04-29 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- PCCW Anniversary Dinner, 2010-04-30 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2010-04-30 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- WCMC-Q Commencement, 2010-05-05 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Global Higher Education Letter, 2010-05-07 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Health Care Conference, 2010-05-11 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- CURW Multi-Faith Panel, 2010-05-11 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Distinguished Faculty Reception, 2010-05-14 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Law School Convocation, 2010-05-16 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Belfer Ground Breaking, 2010-05-26 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Board of Trustees Dinner (Fuchs recognition), 2010-05-28 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Senior Class Campaign, 2010-05-28 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Senior Convocation, 2010-05-29 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- PhD Ceremony, 2010-05-29 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Faculty Awards Dinner with Trustees, 2010-05-29 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Commencement, 2010-05-30 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- WCMC Commencement, 2010-06-03 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Tanner Prize, 2010-06-04 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Icon of the Industry, 2010-06-08 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- Dyson Gift, 2010-06-08 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- American Best Product (Cornell Alumni University), 2010-06-09 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Martin Tang Classroom Dedication, 2010-06-10 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Reunion, 2010-06-10 (Box 13, Folder 43)
- Sanford Weill Q and A, 2010-06-11 (Box 13, Folder 44)
- Olin Lecture, 2010-06-11 (Box 13, Folder 45)
- Reunion State of University Address, 2010-06 (Box 13, Folder 46)
- New Board of Trustee Orientation, 2010-06-16 (Box 13, Folder 47)
- American Society of Health Economics, 2010-06-20 (Box 13, Folder 48)
- Staff Graduation reception, 2010-06-21 (Box 13, Folder 49)
- BHEF, 2010-06-24 (Box 13, Folder 50)
- Miscellany Projects Spring 2010, 2010-06 (Box 13, Folder 51)
- Nike, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 52)
- 2010 Weiss Presidential Fellows, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  Nomination materials
- Assessing the needs of the Law School, 2011 (Box 13, Folder 54)
- Economic Development and Labor Transition Committee (Governor Cuomo), 2010 (Box 13, Folder 55)
- Reimagining Cornell - Bain Hand-off Materials, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 56)
- Reimagining Cornell - Budget Model (Cost of Construction), 2010 (Box 13, Folder 57)
- Reimagining Cornell - Space Inventory and Utilization, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 58)
- Senior Staff Meeting 7/19/2010, 2010-07-19 (Box 13, Folder 59)
- Senior Staff Meeting 8/19/2010, 2010-08-19 (Box 13, Folder 60)
- Senior Staff Meeting 9/7/2010, 2010-09-07 (Box 13, Folder 61)
- Senior Staff Meeting 10/7/2010, 2010-10-07 (Box 13, Folder 62)
- Senior Staff Meeting 11/10/2010, 2010-11-10 (Box 13, Folder 63)
- Senior Staff Meeting 12/6/2010, 2010-12-06 (Box 13, Folder 64)
- Senior Staff Meeting 1/3/2011, 2011-01-03 (Box 13, Folder 65)
- Senior Staff Meeting 1/17/2011, 2011-01-17 (Box 13, Folder 66)
- Senior Staff Meeting 1/31/2011, 2011-01-31 (Box 13, Folder 67)
- Senior Staff Meeting 2/21/2011, 2011-02-21 (Box 13, Folder 68)
- Senior Staff Meeting 2/28/2011, 2011-02-28 (Box 13, Folder 69)
- Senior Staff Meeting 3/28/2011, 2011-03-28 (Box 13, Folder 70)
- Senior Staff Meeting 4/11/2011, 2011-04-11 (Box 13, Folder 71)
- Senior Staff Meeting 4/25/2011, 2011-04-25 (Box 13, Folder 72)
- Senior Staff Meeting 5/16/2011, 2011-05-16 (Box 13, Folder 73)
- Senior Staff Meeting 5/24/2011, 2011-05-24 (Box 13, Folder 74)
- Senior Staff Meeting 6/27/2011, 2011-06-27 (Box 13, Folder 75)
- Association of Public and Land Grant Universities (APLU) Africana Initiative 1 of 2, 2006-2007 (Box 13, Folder 76)
- Association of Public and Land Grant Universities (APLU) Africana Initiative 2 of 2, 2008-2011 (Box 13, Folder 77)
- Consortium on Higher Education Financing (COFHE), 2009-2011 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- King Abdullah University of Science and Technology (KAUST), 2007-2011 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- National Advisory Council of Biomedical Imaging and Bioengineering (NACBIB), 2009-2011 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Cornell Child Care Center - 1 of 2, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Cornell Child Care Center - 2 of 2, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- WCMC Faculty Orientation, 2010-07-15 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- CASE National Conference, 2010-07-18 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Israel Blog, 2010-07-20 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Pre-Freshmen Summer Program, 2010-07-20 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Presidential Impact Video, 2010-07-26 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Real Students Reel Stories, 2010-07-27 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Opatrny Dinner, 2010-08-16 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Physics Grad Students, 2010-08-20 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- New Student Convocation, 2010-08-20 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Welcome Back Message, 2010-08-20 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Tapestry of Possibilities, 2010-08-24 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Suicide Research Project, 2010-08-28 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Mortar Board Gala, 2010-09-10 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Presidential Councilors, 2010-09-13 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Chairman Circle Dinner, 2010-09-15 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Drukier Celebration, 2010-09-20 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Vaclau Klaus Visit, 2010-09-24 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Frank H. T. Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Award, 2010-09-24 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2010-09-24 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Weiss/Lynch Visit, 2010-09-25 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Hartwell Cornell Day, 2010-09-29 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Leeming Literary Lunch, 2010-09-30 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine, 2010-09-28 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Superintendent of Schools, 2010-10-01 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Dyson Reception/Dinner, 2010-10-01 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Vet Diagnostic Lab Opening, 2010-10-01 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Hamlisch Lecture, 2010-10-03 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Miller Dinner, 2010-10-05 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Debi Ostrander Farewell, 2010-10-12 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Leading Cornell, 2010-10-15 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Faculty Senate, 2010-10-13 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Phi Sigma Pi, 2010-10-14 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- CAPE Seminar, 2010-10-14 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- CRP 75th Anniversary, 2010-10-15 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- Bargaining Team Reception, 2010-10-15 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- Phi Beta Sigma, 2010-10-16 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- Harris Lebow Dinner, 2010-10-20 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- 1st Year Parents Weekend, 2010-10-24 (Box 14, Folder 43)
- Access to College Education Region/Institute, 2010-10-20 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- Annual Fund Breakfast, 2010-10-30 (Box 14, Folder 45)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2010-10-22 (Box 14, Folder 46)
- Sustainability Panel, 2010-10-28 (Box 14, Folder 47)
- State of University Address, 2010-10-29 (Box 14, Folder 48)
- D. Streeter Cherry Award Nominating, 2010-10 (Box 14, Folder 49)
- Dermo Grand Rounds, 2010-11-02 (Box 14, Folder 50)
- Credit Swiss Management, 2010-11-05 (Box 14, Folder 51)
- Humanities Op Ed, 2010-11 (Box 14, Folder 52)
- Holocaust Memorial Rededication, 2010-11-07 (Box 14, Folder 53)
- Diversity Update, 2010-11-08 (Box 14, Folder 54)
- Swanson Dedication, 2010-11-11 (Box 14, Folder 55)
- Hatfield Lecture, 2010-11-11 (Box 14, Folder 56)
- Paulson Dinner, 2010-11-11 (Box 14, Folder 57)
- Address to Staff, 2010-11-12 (Box 14, Folder 58)
- Methodist Hospital, 2010-11-17 (Box 14, Folder 59)
- Houston Alumni Association, 2010-11-17 (Box 14, Folder 60)
- Cornell on the Charles, 2010-11-18 (Box 14, Folder 61)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2010-11-23 (Box 14, Folder 62)
- Hesburgh Award Nomination, 2010-11-30 (Box 14, Folder 63)
- Miscellaneous Projects (November), 2010-11 (Box 14, Folder 64)
- BME 4110 Lecture, 2010-12-02 (Box 14, Folder 65)
- Quinonez Literary Lunch, 2010-12-02 (Box 14, Folder 66)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine, 2010-12-03 (Box 14, Folder 67)
- Weill Strategic Planning Dinner, 2010-12-09 (Box 14, Folder 68)
- January Graduates Reception, 2010-12-18 (Box 14, Folder 69)
- Huffington Post Blog Ideas, 2010-12 (Box 14, Folder 70)
- Institute of Medicine Nomination - Hajjar, 2011-01-10 (Box 14, Folder 71)
- Syracuse Post Standard OpEd, 2011-01-12 (Box 14, Folder 72)
- Huffington Post, 2011-01 (Box 14, Folder 73)
- Unitarian Church, 2011-01-16 (Box 14, Folder 74)
- Predictions Dinner, 2011-01-18 (Box 14, Folder 75)
- Gannett Staff Meeting, 2011-01-18 (Box 14, Folder 76)
- President's Circle Dinner, 2011-01-19 (Box 14, Folder 77)
- Institute of Medicine Nomination - Weinstein, 2011-01 (Box 14, Folder 78)
- URA Council of Presidents, 2011-01-25 (Box 14, Folder 79)
- CALC Lunch, 2011-01-29 (Box 14, Folder 80)
- Washington Post Blog, 2011-02-04 (Box 14, Folder 81)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2011-02-04 (Box 14, Folder 82)
- Cornell Minds Matter, 2011-02-04 (Box 14, Folder 83)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine, 2011-02-11 (Box 14, Folder 84)
- Investment Committee, 2011-02-12 (Box 14, Folder 85)
- Boca Brunch, 2011-02-13 (Box 14, Folder 86)
- Palm Beach Dinner, 2011-02-13 (Box 14, Folder 87)
- Pillsbury Dinner, 2011-02-14 (Box 14, Folder 88)
- Harris Dinner, 2011-02-15 (Box 14, Folder 89)
- Responsible Conduct in Research, 2011-02-23 (Box 14, Folder 90)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2011-02 (Box 14, Folder 91)
- Iscol Lecture, 2011-02-24 (Box 14, Folder 92)
- Huffington Post, 2011-02 (Box 14, Folder 93)
- Diwan Foundation, 2011-02-25 (Box 14, Folder 94)
- 400 Club Breakfast, 2011-02-28 (Box 14, Folder 95)
- George Desdunes Service, 2011-03-02 (Box 14, Folder 96)
- R. Daines Funeral, 2011-03-02 (Box 14, Folder 97)
- Tisch Strategic Planning Dinner, 2011-03-02 (Box 14, Folder 98)
- Chancellor Zimpher Visit, 2011-03-04 (Box 14, Folder 99)
- Latino Studies Faculty, 2011-03-04 (Box 14, Folder 100)
- PCCW, 2011-03-04 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- National Humanities Alliance, 2011-03-07 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Perkins Prize, 2011-03-08 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Tata Nano Symposium, 2011-03-10 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Distinguished Chair Holders, 2011-03-11 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- LA Campus Event, 2011-03-14 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- CSV Advisory Council, 2011-03-14 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- CSV '11 Event, 2011-03-15 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2011-03-24 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Decision Making Letter, 2011-03 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- FASEB, 3/24-25/2011 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Kintner Memorial, 2011-03-26 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Middle States Visit, 3/27-30/2011 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- D. Barber Intro (RLD), 2011-03-28 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Doc. On Race, 2011-03-29 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- SAE Message to Parents, 2011-03-29 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Service Recognition Awards Dinner, 2011-03-31 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine, 2011-04-01 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Feeney Video, 2011-04 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Huffington Post Soft Power, 2011-04 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Cornell Days, 2011-04-11 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Senior Class Reception, 2011-04-11 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Saudi Arabia, 2011-04 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Saudi Arabia Opening, 2011-04-19 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Tata Dinner, 2011-04-15 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2011-04-29 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Parents Campus Visit, 2011-04-29 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- WCMC-Q Commencement, 2011-05-04 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- International White Paper, 2011-05-09 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Stocking Hall Groundbreaking, 2011-05-09 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Prostate Cancer/Robotic Surgery, 2011-05-10 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Tower Club Dinner, 2011-05-10 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Dr. Hajjar Fulbright Celebration, 2011-05-11 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Frank Robinson Retirement, 2011-05-12 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Feldshuh Recognition, 2011-05-16 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Ravli Institute, 2011-05-17 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Joint Service Clubs, 2011-05-18 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Distinguished Faculty Reception, 2011-05-18 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Humanities Caucus Roundtable, 2011-05-19 (Box 15, Folder 39)
- WCMC Commencement, 2011-05-23 (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Leading Cornell Presentation, 2011-05-24 (Box 15, Folder 41)
- Staff Graduates Reception, 2011-05-24 (Box 15, Folder 42)
- Merrill Scholars, 2011-05-25 (Box 15, Folder 43)
- Rawlings Farewell, 2011-05-25 (Box 15, Folder 44)
- Miscellaneous Projects (Fall/Spring), 2011-05 (Box 15, Folder 45)
- Commencement Info, 2011-05 (Box 15, Folder 46)
- CCA/Mental Health Panel, 2011-06-03 (Box 15, Folder 47)
- Tanner Prize, 2011-06-06 (Box 15, Folder 48)
- Icon of the Industry, 2011-06-07 (Box 15, Folder 49)
- Alvin Alley, 2011-06-08 (Box 15, Folder 50)
- Olin Lecture, 2011-06-10 (Box 15, Folder 51)
- Altman Bench Dedication, 2011-06-11 (Box 15, Folder 52)
- Ken Goldman Foremost Benefactor, 2011-06-11 (Box 15, Folder 53)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine, 2011-06 (Box 15, Folder 54)
- Reunion State of University Address, 2011-06-11 (Box 15, Folder 55)
- Huffington Post, 2011-06-11 (Box 15, Folder 56)
- Report of the President, 2011-06-11 (Box 15, Folder 57)
- Marioni Event, 2011-06-19 (Box 15, Folder 58)
- Ivy Plus, 2011-06-21 (Box 15, Folder 59)
- Groos Foremost Benefactor, 2011-06-22 (Box 15, Folder 60)
- Today Show, 2011-06-30 (Box 15, Folder 61)
- Affirmative Action Plan, 2011-06 (Box 15, Folder 62)
- Report of the President, 2011-05 (Box 15, Folder 63)
- Senior Class Reception, 2011-05-27 (Box 15, Folder 64)
- Board of Trustees Dinner, 2011-05-27 (Box 15, Folder 65)
- Convocation, 2011-05-28 (Box 15, Folder 66)
- PhD Ceremony, 2011-05-28 (Box 15, Folder 67)
- Faculty Awards Dinner with Trustees, 2011-05-28 (Box 15, Folder 68)
- NIAA (National Institute on Alcohol Abuse and Alcoholism) College Presidents Working Group (and Dartmouth Collaborative), 2010-2012 (Box 15, Folder 69)
- President's Advisory Group, 2010-2012 (Box 15, Folder 70)
- Sigma Alpha Epsilon, 2011 (Box 15, Folder 71)
- 2011 Weiss Presidential Fellows, 2011 (Box 15, Folder 72)
- Cornell Alumni Magazines, 2012 (Box 15, Folder 73)
- Hazing Policies, 2011 (Box 15, Folder 74)
- Hazing Policies - New York Times Opinion/Editorial, 2011 (Box 15, Folder 75)
- Immigration Congressional Testimony July, 2011, 2011 (Box 15, Folder 76)
  Correspondence/Testimony
- Internationalization Task Force Committee, 2011-2012 (Box 15, Folder 77)
  Correspondence; Skorton White Paper "Bringing Cornell to the World and the World to Cornell"
- Middle States Accreditation 1 of 2, 2011-2012 (Box 15, Folder 78)
- Middle States Accreditation 2 of 2, 2011-2012 (Box 15, Folder 79)
- Pledging Opinion/Editorial, 2011 (Box 15, Folder 80)
- President's Family Work and Family Life Committee, 2011-2012 (Box 15, Folder 81)
  Correspondence/meeting materials
- Southern Tier Regional Council 1 of 3, 2011-2012 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Southern Tier Regional Council 2 of 3, 2011-2012 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Southern Tier Regional Council 3 of 3, 2011-2012 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities (cIcu), 2009-2012 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Financial Aid, 2008-2012 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Law School Self-Study 2/28/2011, 2011-2012 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Partnership for New York City, 2006-2011 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- 2012 Weiss Presidential Fellows, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Adidas Issue, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Bias Incidents/Sexual Assaults [Assembly4Justice], 2012-2013 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Cornell Daily Sun Column on Divestment April 2013, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Cornell Daily Sun Column on Immigration Feb. 2013, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Corson Memorial 9/8/12, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Cuomo Tax Free New York, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Feeney (Founding Chairman), 2012-2013 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Forbes Blog (Guns) Feb. 2013, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Gates/HCM Financial Aid, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Ho Plaza Protests 11/19/2012, 2012-2013 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Immigration Blog (for Physicians) Feb. 2013, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Immigration Day Event 4/19/2013, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- India Essay (International Briefing for Higher Education) 11/10/12, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- President's Family Work and Family Life Committee, 2012-2013 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Ratan Tata - Cornell Agr and Nutrition Initiative, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Ratan Tata and India Higher Education Initiative, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Ratan Tata Tribute 8/15/12, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Southern Tier Presentation 10/23/12, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Southern Tier Regional Council, 2012-2013 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Administrative Streamlining Program (formerly Reimagining Cornell), 2010-2013 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Cornell NYC Tech -- Proposal and Appendix (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Cornell NYC Tech 1 of 3, 2011-2013 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Cornell NYC Tech 2 of 3, 2011-2013 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Cornell NYC Tech 3 of 3, 2011-2013 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Cornell NYC Tech - NYC Mayor/City, 2013 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Cornell NYC Tech -- Fundraising, 2012-2013 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Cornell NYC Tech -- Jacobs Technion-Cornell Innovation Institute (JTCII), 2012-2013 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Cornell NYC Tech -- External Affairs, 2012 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Cornell NYC Tech -- Corporate Advisory Board, 2012 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Cornell NYC Tech -- Board of Trustees Task Force, 2012-2013 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Cornell NYC Tech -- Core Team, 2012 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Cornell NYC Tech -- Roosevelt Island, 2012 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Cornell NYC Tech -- Technion, 2011-2012 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  Correspondence. Also CD-4618 Technion President Peretz Lavie American Jewish Committee Dinner 6-18-12
- Cornell NYC Tech -- Department of Commerce/USPTO (United States Patent and Trademark Office), 2012 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Cornell NYC Tech -- Atlantic Philanthropic Service 1 of 2, 2011-2012 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Cornell NYC Tech -- Atlantic Philanthropic Service 2 of 2, 2012-2013 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Gas Drilling, 2009-2012 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Internationalization White Paper, 2010-2012 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Hot Spot / Incubator / Innovation NY / Start-up NY, 2012-2014 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Toward New Destinations (Diversity Initiative), 2012-2014 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  Correspondence/Report
- 2013 Weiss Presidential Fellows, 2013 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- 2014 Weiss Presidential Fellows, 2014 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Fossil Fuels/Renewable Energy, 2014 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- President's Family Work and Family Life Committee, 2013-2014 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- 2011 Employee Survey and Follow-up, 2010-2013 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Atlantic Philanthropies, 2011-2013 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Cornell Community Contribution, 2008-2014 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Goldman Sachs 10,000 Small Business Consortium, 2009-2013 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Governor of New York, 2008-2013 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Ivy League Council 1 of 2, 2011-2014 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Ivy League Council 2 of 2, 2009-2010 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- University Diversity Council (UDC), 2009-2014 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Coalition of Angry Students, 2014-2015 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Cornell NYC Tech -- Steering Committee, 2013-2015 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Fair Labor Association, 2011-2014 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Ivy League Council Concussion Imitative 1 of 3, 2011-2014 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Ivy League Council Concussion Imitative 2 of 3, 2011-2014 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Ivy League Council Concussion Imitative 3 of 3, 2011-2014 (Box 18, Folder 22)